(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun 〜The Greatest Idols, You Have to Stan Them!〜
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
2nd Merchandise Release
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Attention
To our visitors:
Please be aware of flashing lights due to stage effects.
Cheering loudly is OK!
2次販売グッズ
2nd Round Merchandise
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon
たくさんの素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！
ぜひ「あいあいあい」も楽しんでくださいね！
Thank you for so many wonderful short videos!
Please enjoy "Ai Ai Ai" as well!
だから...
So...
君のこと
it's you that I...
大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
love, love, love, love, love so much!
溢れるこの愛 きっと止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop!
あいあいあい I love you
Ai ai ai I love you!
君もあいあいあい I need you
You too, ai ai ai I need you!
もっと もっと
More and more!
動画ありがとうございました！ぜひ『あいあいあいあいあいふゆー』を使って動画を作ってみてください！
Thank you for the video! Please try making a video using "Ai Ai Ai Ai Ai I Love You"!
好きなったけ愛してて
Love me as much as you like
夢見るハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming heart goes boing boing boing
穴に落ちてあみゃあみゃ
Falling into the hole, amya amya
こんなになってもいまだに抜け出せない！
Even like this, I still can't break free!
どうしたもんかな　ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui nui nui
助けて君たち　あほいほいほい
Help me, everyone! Ahoy hoy hoy
待って　待って　待って　待って
Wait, wait, wait, wait
好きなったけ愛してね
Please love me as much as you like
最凶アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The ultimate idols, you have no choice but to support them~ The concert will be starting soon...
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
アニメにハマって…
Hooked on anime...
歌いたくなっちゃった!
I just had to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて…
Being able to sing karaoke while watching scenes of my favorite...
尊すぎてツラいっ!
It's so precious it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう!
Let's find the song you want to sing!
JOYSOUND!
全国のアミューズメント施設にてホロライブ3期生プライズ順次展開中!
Hololive 3rd Gen prizes are now being rolled out at amusement centers nationwide!
パペットぬいぐるみ、
Puppet plushies,
寝そべりミニマスコット、
Nesoberi mini mascots,
大判マウスパッド。
and large mousepads.
全国のアミューズメント施設でゲットしてね!
Get them at amusement centers nationwide!
詳しくはキャラ広場を検索! FuRyu.
Search 'Chara-hiroba' for more details! FuRyu.
吉野家でごはんしょ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya♪
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Enjoy the spirit of the original.
牛丼は吉野家。
Beef bowls are Yoshinoya.
今日も、吉野家日和です。
Today is another perfect day for Yoshinoya.
ホロライブ3期生ミニCDコレクション。
Hololive 3rd Gen Mini CD Collection.
ライブ会場スペシャルラインナップバージョン!
Live venue special lineup version!
1回500円。
500 yen per turn.
CDプレートやジャケットカードが取り出せるよ。
You can take out the CD plate and jacket card.
つながるあくりるますこっとも好評発売中!
Connectable acrylic mascots are also now on sale!
ライブ会場でチェックしてね!
Check them out at the live venue!
きゅるるん大作戦
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun
~The Strongest Idols, You Have No Choice But to Support Them~
本日は、
Today,
ホロライブ...
hololive...
ホロライブ サードジェネレーションライブ
hololive 3rd Generation Live
『きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜』に
to 'Kyururun Daisakusen ~Saikyou Idol, Osushikanaidesho~'!
ご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming today!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、
To ensure everyone enjoys the live until the end,
いくつかご案内させていただきます。
I have a few announcements to make.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell,
無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
don't push yourself and please inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Mosh, dive, and throwing objects onto the stage,
他の皆様の迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
as well as any actions that bother others or disrupt the performance, are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
また、本公演は映像配信、および、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Also, during this performance, cameras for the stream and photography will be present,
客席が映り込む場合があります。
and the audience may be shown on screen.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションなどに使用される可能性がありますので、
These videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes,
あらかじめご了承ください。
so please be aware of this in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#きゅるるん大作戦DAY2」です。
Also, the live hashtag is #KyururunDaisakusenDAY2.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくださいね！
Please use the hashtag to help spread the excitement!
それでは、開演まであと少しです。
Now, there's just a little time left before the show starts.
君たちの声をいっぱい聞かせてください！
Please let us hear your voices loud and clear!
そして、今からちょっと3期生で円陣を組もうと思っているんですが、
And now, the 3rd generation members are going to do a huddle together,
えっと、マイクを通さずやりますので、ちょっと静かにして、
but, since we'll be doing it without microphones, please be a little quiet,
あの、みんな耳を澄ませていただければ、お願いします。
and if everyone could listen closely, we'd appreciate it.
行くんで、ちょっとシーンと待ってててください。
We're going to do it now, so please wait quietly.
行きます！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready!
ホロライブ！
hololive!
3期生！
3rd Generation!
きゅるるん！
Kyururun!
おー！
Oh!
こんぺこ！
Konpeko!
こんぬいー！
Kon-nui!
Ahoy!
超アイドル宣言ガールは　欲張り
Super Idol Declaration Girls are greedy
笑い合って　もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we'll become even cuter
Oh Yeah Yeah
遠いようで　近くて
Seems far, yet so close
他人なのに　家族みたいで
Even though we're strangers, we're like a family
レボリューション？
Revolution?
狂うなハイセッション
Don't go crazy, high session
喜怒哀楽を分かち合ってさ
Sharing our joys and sorrows
デカくなって行きたいよね
We want to keep growing bigger
でも小さな事も大事にして
But let's also cherish the small things
一歩ずつ　刻んで
Carving it out, step by step
楽しんでくれるのが　嬉しい
Seeing you enjoy yourself makes us happy
僕らのエンターテイナー
Our entertainer
後ろまで見えてる
We can see all the way to the back
画面の向こうも届いてる
Reaching out to those behind the screens too
光の海を泳ぐのさ
Swimming through a sea of lights
超アイドル宣言ガールは　欲張り
Super Idol Declaration Girls are greedy
愛されたい　認められたい　君とじゃなきゃ　嫌だ
Wanting to be loved, wanting to be recognized, it has to be with you
絶好調です　狙い撃ちで　君にウインク
We're in top form, aiming a wink right at you
やっぱ宣言ガールで　めっちゃハッピー
As expected, being Declaration Girls makes us so happy
あれもしたい　これもしたい
Wanting to do this, wanting to do that
叶えちゃう　ヤッタ！
We'll make it happen, yay!
全力走る　もちろん君と
Running with all our might, of course with you
笑い合って　もっと可愛くなる
Laughing together, we'll become even cuter
Oh Yeah Yeah
せっかくだから　やりきりたい！
Since we're here, we want to give it our all!
乗り越えるべき壁もデカい
The walls we must overcome are also huge
トライ＆エンタメで
With try and entertainment
君が思ってるよりずっと
Much more than you might think
君のこと想ってる
We're thinking of you
どうかな？　焦がれた
How is it? The dream we yearned for
夢には近づけてるかな？
Are we getting any closer to it?
これがあるから頑張れるんだ
This is why we can keep working hard
聞かせて
Let us hear you
1, 2, 3, 4!
もう最高宣言ガールは　幸せ
Now, the Best Declaration Girls are happy
愛されていて　伸び代あって　下向くとか　ヤダ
Being loved, having room to grow, we hate looking down
テンポアップし　続けて行く　未来景色
Speeding up, continuing on to the future scenery
世界に届けて
Reaching out to the world
限界突破で
Breaking through our limits
今すぐ達成
Achieving it right now
みんなで作ってく
Building it together with everyone
イェイ！
Yay!
DAY2も盛り上がっていくぞー！
Day 2 is gonna be even more hyped!
君たちまだまだ声出せますよねー！
You guys can still shout even more, right?!
意志揺らいでも頑張っちゃう
Even if my will wavers, I'll do my best
褒められて伸びるのは勝ってるよね
I know I thrive on praise, right?
本能的分が宝物
My instinctive side is a treasure
ねぇ 構わないよ 笑う
Hey, I don't mind, I'll laugh
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
超アイドル伝道ガールは欲張り
The super idol missionary girl is greedy
愛されたいし夢だって見てみたい 君とじゃなきゃ
I want to be loved and I want to dream, it has to be with you
やっぱ絶好調です 願いを打ちで
After all, I'm in top form, firing my wishes
君にウインク
Winking at you
やっぱ超アイドル伝道ガールでめちゃハッピー
After all, being a super idol missionary girl makes me so happy
あれもしたいしこれもしたい 叶っちゃう
I want to do this and that, they're coming true
全速で走る もちろん君と
Running at full speed, of course with you
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
Smiling together, I'll become even cuter
どこまでも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like I can go anywhere
Oh Yeah Yeah!
今日はこのままさよならじゃないよ
Today isn't just goodbye like this
手をとってくれたなら
If you've taken my hand
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
On a night when even secrets fall asleep
君を連れていくよ
I'll take you with me
それは例えば遠く離れてたって
Even if, for example, we were far apart
手を繋いでいられるような奇跡のような
Like a miracle that lets us keep holding hands
話をしよう 窓は開けといて
Let's talk, keep the window open
今日までを思い出して
Thinking back on everything until today
一つ一つ並べたら
If we line them up one by one
明日の雨が気になりだして
I start to worry about tomorrow's rain
どうも眠れないみたいだ
It seems I can't sleep at all
変わりたくないことや
Things I don't want to change
変わらなきゃいけないことも
And things that have to change
少し忘れたまま窓の外 眺めていたんだ
I was looking out the window, having forgotten a bit
あぁ 雨が降り出すその前に
Ah, before the rain starts falling
君のところまで行けるような気がして
I feel like I can make it to where you are
目を閉じてみたんだ
I tried closing my eyes
そしてこのまま遠くへといこう
And let's go far away just like this
手をとってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll take my hand
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
A night when even secrets fall asleep
君と泳いでいくよ
I'll swim through it with you
街の明かりが消えるたびに笑って
Smiling every time the city lights go out
路地裏で抱き合おう
Let's embrace in a back alley
馬鹿みたいな話をしよう
Let's talk about stupid things
窓は開けといて
Keep the window open
聞こえる
I can hear it
次はマリン！
Next is Marine!
君たち、二日目も盛り上がっていきますよ！
Everyone, let's keep the energy high on day 2 as well!
言い訳バニー！
Iiwake Bunny!
どっちが好きなのよ！
Which one do you like!
なんとかかんないかな
Can't we do something about this?
ラビラビ
Labi Labi
隣のあいつが邪魔だな
That person next to me is in the way
良くないそんなこと
That's not good
ダメダメだ
It's no good, no good
前代未聞絶対
Unprecedented, definitely
どわどわ違うな
Dowa dowa, that's not right
何だって競争
Everything is a competition
逃げ出せそういうの
Run away from stuff like that
なんだか寂しい
Somehow it's lonely
ムズムズしちゃう
It's making me restless
内緒話シークレット
A secret talk, secret
ベタ惚れどっちかセレクト
Head over heels, select one
あの子にゃ負けない
I won't lose to that girl
今更ジェラシー
Jealousy at this late stage
欲張りね
You're greedy, aren't you?
欲張りか？
Am I greedy?
してあります
It's already done
お！
Oh!
言わなきゃ手は合ってる
Our hands meet without saying a word
ああでもない
Not like that
こうでもない
Not like this
やめにしなさい
Stop it
つらぬけ舞舞舞舞
Go through it, Dance Dance Dance Dance
言い訳バニー
Excuse Bunny
自由だの悠々
Freedom and leisure
簡単
Simple
ハニバニダリダリマジな話
Honey Bunny Dari Dari, serious talk
どっち どっち
Which one? Which one?
が好きなのよ！
Do you like!
ダメダメダメ
No no no
よそ見しないで
Don't look away
ダメダメダメ
No no no
抜け出したい
I want to break free
今日は私の方
Today is my turn
でしょでしょ
Right? Right?
どうしまして
How about it?
反対方向
Opposite direction
One, Two!
息がつまないわけじゃない 地団駄の優柔不断
It's not like I can't breathe, it's just indecisive stamping.
ダダダ ハニバニダリダリ まじな話 どっちが好きなのよ
Da-da-da, honey bunny, dally dally... seriously, which one do you like?
ダメダメダメ よそ見しないで
No, no, no! Don't look away.
ダメダメダメ もう逃げ出したい
No, no, no! I want to run away already.
ゲコやるしかない
But I've just gotta do it.
ショーミー ちゃんと示せ 反対方向
Show me, show it properly, the opposite direction.
WANTED!
言い訳ばかり
Nothing but excuses.
そばにいて
Stay by my side.
言い訳ばかり
Nothing but excuses.
あー
Ah—
次は、ぺこら！
Next up is Pekora!
全力ジャンピング！いくぺこよー！
All-out jumping! Let's go-peko!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
魔法をかけたくなしで 歌いながら気の向く方へ
Without wishing for magic, I sing my way toward wherever I please.
迷ってるの？
Are you lost?
冒険してるの？
Are you on an adventure?
それは、みんな次第
Well, that's all up to you!
まだまだ楽しみ足りない
I still haven't had enough fun.
でもでも時間が足りない
But there's just not enough time.
ワクワクする明日へ
Toward an exciting tomorrow.
思い切って 張り切って
Take the plunge, get fired up,
前向いてさ 進もう
Look forward, and let's go!
せーの！
One, two!
歌って本気で
Sing with all your might!
跳び尽くしちゃえ
Jump 'til you can't jump anymore!
急ぎ過ぎくらいで
Even if it's a bit too fast,
It's all right!
早起きよりも
Rather than waking up early,
よっしゃおー！
Let's go—!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because things will work out somehow.
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
Because a pinch can become a chance.
It's all OK!
みんなで笑えば無敵だよね
We're invincible when we're laughing together!
It's all OK!
何だか全力で
Somehow, with all our might,
跳び尽くしちゃって
Let's jump 'til we drop!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings!
ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプで飛び出そう
Let's leap out with a hop, step, and a jump!
なかなか お布団から出られない日もある
There are days when you just can't get out of bed.
でも明日から そう明日から
But starting tomorrow—yes, starting tomorrow,
本気を出すんだ
I'm going to get serious!
陽が差すまで
Until the sun shines,
陽が暮れるまで
Until the sun sets,
無限な楽しみで
With infinite fun,
It's all right!
早起きよりも
Rather than waking up early,
よっしゃおー！
Let's go—!
なんとかなっちゃうはずだから
Because things will work out somehow.
ピンチはチャンスになるからさ
Because a pinch can become a chance.
It's all OK!
みんなで笑えば無敵だよね
We're invincible when we're laughing together!
It's all OK!
何だか全力で
Somehow, with all our might,
跳び尽くしちゃって
Let's jump 'til we drop!
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings!
ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプで飛び出そう
Let's leap out with a hop, step, and a jump!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
最後は、ノエル！
And finally, Noel!
あーい！
Yes!
みんな！シャックルメドレー最後まで盛り上がっていくぞー！
Everyone! Let's get fired up until the very end of this Shakkuru Medley!
苦い恋の果て 残された出所不明の金の山
At the end of a bitter love, a mountain of gold of unknown origin remains.
アイツの気配がするもの は未練ばかりで食えやしない
The things that smell of him are nothing but regrets, not fit for consumption.
私はいきながら 負けて出る鏡の前で早変わり
Even while I live, I'm a quick-change artist in front of the mirror of defeat.
パイパイ仮面で如何かしら？ 今宵も一暴れ
How about the Pai Pai Mask? Going on a rampage again tonight!
踊れ 踊り踊れ 乱れ髪はずむ胸
Dance, dance, dance! Disheveled hair and a beating heart.
透明の罠に酔いしれて
Intoxicated by an invisible trap.
シャヤスポット！
Shaya-spot!
シャヤスポット ライトを皆！
Shaya-spot! Give me the light, everyone!
パイヤ！
Paiya!
パパパパイヤ！
Pa-pa-pa-paiya!
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
The Pai Pai Mask is a billionaire!
パイヤ！
Paiya!
パパパパイヤ！
Pa-pa-pa-paiya!
黄金の蝶舞い上がれ
Golden butterflies, take flight!
ホーヤ！
Hoya!
ホー踊れよ！
Ho— keep dancing!
三財万歳 恋シャワー
Wealth and fortune banzai, love shower!
セーナ！
Sena!
セー生きろよ！
Se— live your life!
瞬間クライマックス
The ultimate climax!
浮世 忘れて老ける ダッシングハイ
Forget the world and grow old, dashing high!
パイパイヤ
Pai-paiya!
ディスコティックな
Discotheque-style...
パイパイ仮面
Pai Pai Mask!
パイ！
Pai!
パパイヤ！
Papaiya!
パパパパイヤ！
Pa-pa-pa-paiya!
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
The Pai Pai Mask is a billionaire!
パイヤ！
Paiya!
パッパ！
Pappa!
パイ パパパパ パイ パパパ パ パイ 黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Pai papapapa pai papapa pa pai, golden butterfly, soar up high.
ホイ せや！ ホイ せや！ 踊れよ 三拝 三拝 ポイ シャワー
Hoi, seya! Hoi, seya! Let's dance! Three bows, three bows, poi shower.
セイ！ すな！ ホイ 生きろよ 瞬間 クライマックス
Seya! Suna! Hoi, live for the moment! Instant climax!
浮世 忘れて 老ける 舵 が ハイ ハイハイ ハイハイ
Forget the world, the rudder grows old, hai haihai haihai.
ディスコ ティック クイーン
Disco-tic queen.
バイバイ仮面
Bye-bye mask.
イエーイ！
Yeeeeeeah!
Day 2！ Day 2スタート！
Day 2! Day 2 start!
じゃあ早速自己紹介からしていきますか？
Well then, shall we start with the introductions?
していきましょう！ はい！
Let's do it! / Okay!
じゃあみんな、ぺこら久しぶりのあの挨拶行くから、わかるよねみんな？あの挨拶だよ！
Alright everyone, Pekora's going to do that greeting for the first time in a while. You all know it, right? That greeting!
どの挨拶だ？ あれだ！ あれしかない！
Which one is it? / That one! / It has to be that one!
行くぞ！ ドンドンガドンドン！ 全人類VTuber... 全人類...
Here we go! Dodon-ga-dodon! All-humanity VTuber... all-humanity...
え、大丈夫か？
Uh, are you okay?
もう一度、もう一回ね！ 行きます！
Once more, one more time! Here I go!
ドンドンガドンドン！ 全VTuber一超絶可愛いの誰だ？ ドンドンガドンドン！
Dodon-ga-dodon! Who's the most super-extra-cute of all VTubers? Dodon-ga-dodon!
ぺこらっちゃおー！
Pekora-cchao!
やっとできました！ ありがとう！ あー！
Finally got it! Thank you! Ah!
じゃあ次はフレアん。
Next is Flare-n.
はい、じゃあフレアは、はいダーリンって言うので、はいハニーって返してください。
Okay, so I'll say 'Hi Darling,' so please respond with 'Hi Honey.'
OK!
行きますよ！ はいダーリン！
Here I go! Hi Darling!
はいハニー！
Hi Honey!
あーありがとう！ ホロライブ3期生不知火フレアです！ そして？
Ah, thank you! I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive's 3rd generation! And next?
はい、えーどうしようかな... え、じゃあコンまっするーって言うから普通にコンまっするーで。
Okay, hmm what should I do... Oh, then I'll say 'Kon-massuru,' so just respond with 'Kon-massuru.'
牛丼も？ 牛丼はまあ...
What about gyudon too? Well, gyudon is...
あ、やべやべ... あ、何でもない何でもない！ よし行くぞ！
Ah, oops... Ah, never mind, never mind! Alright, here we go!
せーの、コンまっするー！
One, two, Kon-massuru!
コンまっするー！
Kon-massuru!
はい、ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！ そして？
Yes, I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive's 3rd generation! And next?
キミたち！ 本物のバイバイ仮面は誰ー！？
You guys! Who's the real Bye-bye Mask!?
マリン！ マリン！
Marine! Marine!
バイバイ仮面！ バイバイ仮面！
Bye-bye mask! Bye-bye mask!
ねえ昨日からさ、ぺこらに船長取られるし、ノエルにバイバイ仮面...
Hey, since yesterday, Pekora took 'Captain' and Noel took 'Bye-bye Mask'...
船長です！ 本物のバイバイ仮面だー！
I'm the Captain! / It's the real Bye-bye Mask!
本物のバイバイ仮面が奪われたわけですね。 ほー、悲しい。
So the real Bye-bye Mask was stolen. How sad.
ということでね、はい、ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Anyway, yes, I'm Houshou Marine, Captain of the Houshou Pirates from Hololive's 3rd generation!
いやついにDay 2！ Day 2ですよ！ ん？ 昨日と衣装違くない？
Wow, finally Day 2! It's Day 2! Hmm? Isn't the outfit different from yesterday?
ねえ！
Yeah!
分かりましたか皆さん。 なんか昨日とちょっと、悪魔になっちゃった！
Did you all notice? Something's a bit different from yesterday... I've become a demon!
あら！
Oh!
あ、ちょっと悪魔っぽくなってしまったかな？
Ah, did I become a bit devilish?
そうなんですよね。 実はこれ初めて公開するんですよ。 みんなびっくりしたかな？
That's right. Actually, this is the first time we're showing this. Was everyone surprised?
かわいい！ ありがとう！
Cute! Thank you!
え、でも悪魔、なんか結構マリンは小悪魔系で売ってるんで、かなりシナジーあるかなって。
But since I usually brand myself as a little devil, I think there's a lot of synergy.
ぺこらも小悪魔系で売ってるから... あ、悪魔...
I brand myself as a little devil too... Oh, demon...
変な悪魔いない？ 嫌な奴きた！
Isn't there a weird demon? A nasty one showed up!
天使と悪魔どっちが好きキミたち？ あ、確かに。 じゃあハイで言ってもらえば？
Which do you like, angels or demons? Oh, true. Then how about you tell us with a shout?
ペンライトの色とか。 白と赤？
With penlight colors. White and red?
じゃあ悪魔派は赤。 天使派は白。
Then demon fans use red. Angel fans use white.
じゃあ皆さん変えてください！ 掲げてください！
Then everyone, please change your colors! Hold them up high!
お、結構いい感じに割れてる！ 若干赤が多いか？ 悪魔の方が人気？ でもハーフハーフか。
Oh, it's split pretty well! Maybe a bit more red? Are demons more popular? But it looks fifty-fifty.
いいですね。 これを拝めてよかったね。
It's nice. It's good we got to see this.
そしてDay 1に引き続き、バンドも生演奏となっております！
And just like Day 1, we have a live band performance!
かっこいいですね、これねー
This looks so cool, doesn't it?
可愛いー！
So cute!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
嬉しいですよ
I'm so happy.
そして配信のコメントももちろん見てるぺこー！
And of course I'm watching the stream comments too, peko!
コメントのみんなー！
To everyone in the comments!
もうもちろん会場のみんなももちろんあたりまえー！
And of course, everyone here in the venue too!
みんな素敵な気合の入った推し活ファッションしてきてくれてありがとうー！
Thank you everyone for coming in such great fandom outfits with so much spirit!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
可愛いー！
So cute!
最高、最高ですよ
It's the best, really the best.
いや、もう、ちょっぱな、シャッフルメドレーでしたけどー
Man, we kicked things off with the shuffle medley...
凄かったよね！
It was amazing, right?
アゲアゲだったよね！
It was so hype!
でもですね、なんとですね、ここまでのー
But, you know what? Up until now...
冒頭無料チラ見せが、終了となります！
The free opening sneak peek is coming to an end!
えー！？そんなー、嘘だー、嘘でしょー！
What?! No way! You're kidding, right?!
嘘だぺこー！
You're lying, peko!
嘘じゃないぺこですね
It's not a lie-peko.
でも、みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから、
But since I'm sure everyone wants to keep watching,
概要欄に配信チケットリンクあるので、今、ポチポチっと買って見てみてください！
there's a ticket link in the description, so please click and buy one now to keep watching!
お願いします！
Please!
今日は凄い、今日も、むしろ昨日よりブチ上がってるから！
It's crazy today—even more hype than yesterday!
もうブチ上げブチ上げで準備してますから！
We're all set to keep the energy through the roof!
Day 1とは違ったね、良さ、盛り上がり、そう、もう、君たちも今日超ブチ上がりなんで！
The energy is different from Day 1, and you guys are absolutely fired up today!
頑張って最後まで息切れしないようにブチ上がってください！
Keep that energy up and stay hype until the very end without burning out!
しっかり声出してねー！
Make some noise!
そしてね、配信で楽しんでる人は、
And for those enjoying the stream,
ハッシュタグ『きゅるるん大作戦Day2』でいっぱい呟いてください！
please tweet a lot using the hashtag #KyururunDaisakusenDay2!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
じゃあ、ドキドキするね、そろそろいいですか？
Alright, I'm getting nervous. Are you ready?
行きますか？次の曲に行ってみてもいいでしょうか？
Shall we go? Can we move on to the next song?
行っちゃいましょう！
Let's do it!
ではですね、次の曲は、なんと私からスタートさせていただく...
Well then, the next song actually starts with me...
おおー、何が来るの？
Oh! What's coming?
じゃあ次の曲、行きましょう！フルアメドレー！
Then let's go to the next song! Furua Medley!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.